{
    "id": "e844903d8af34811b5ecc0bd926d2700",
    "title": "Conjunctive adverbs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a7026eae70c14751b5b56f9504e98646",
            "title": "Conjunctive Adverbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Vegetables are rich sources of vitamins and antioxidants and ……………… eating vegetables is essential for good health.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "as",
                        "hence"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘The last bus has gone.’ ‘………………….., we are going to have to walk.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Therefore",
                        "As",
                        "Then"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… the starter, I thought the meal was nice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Apart from",
                        "Besides",
                        "In addition"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I bought that car. It looked good and, ………………….., it was reasonably priced.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "besides",
                        "moreover"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Studies seem to suggest that bright blue and bright yellow are the most visible and ………………….. the safest colors for vehicles.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "therefore",
                        "also"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better mend your ways ………………….., you will land in serious trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hence",
                        "otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She didn’t leave her husband ………………….. the fact that he had cheated on her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "although",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. each individual is unique in many ways, members of the same species share many common characteristics.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "Although",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They have recruited more people and …………………. the service has improved",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as result",
                        "as consequence",
                        "consequently"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was not confident of winning. …………………, I decided to give it a try.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "So",
                        "Nevertheless",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}